流|<な#|がれてく 時|<と#|きの中|<な#|かででも
Never figured out what it meant to keep on living,
即便置身于 奔腾的时光长河中
na ga re te ku to ki no na ka de de mo
気|<けだるさが ほらグルグル廻|<ま#|わって
Somewhere in my mind, spinning round and round in circles thinking
这份倦怠感 依旧萦绕在身难以消弭
ke da ru sa ga ho ra gu ru gu ru ma wa tte
私|<わ#|た#|しから離|<は#|なれる心|<こ#|こ#|ろも見|<みえないわ
Every single time - tell me what I'm missing?
最初的本心 也已与我渐行渐远 难以再看清
wa ta shi ka ra ha na re ru ko ko ro mo mi e na i wa
そう 知|<しらない？
Is it somewhere deep inside, maybe I just lost it?
这样你明白吗？
so u shi ra na i
自|<じ分|ぶ#|んから動|<う#|ごくこともなく
Even if I stay, never move, my body's frozen
只因我自己 早已不想作出改变
ji bun ka ra u go ku ko to mo na ku
時|<と#|きの隙|<す#|き|間|まに流|<な#|がされ続|<つ#|づけて
Measure every day, every minute, every second slowly
任时光飞逝 自身投入其中随波逐流
to ki no su ki ma ni na ga sa re tsu zu ke te
知|<しらないわ 周|<ま#|わりのことなど
What you wanna say, doesn't make one difference
周遭的一切 皆已与我毫无瓜葛
shi ra na i wa ma wa ri no ko to na do
私|<わ#|た#|しは私|<わ#|た#|し それだけ
Like I need to be okay, you don't have to save me
我也只是我自己 仅 此 而 已！
wa ta shi wa wa ta shi so re da ke
夢|<ゆ#|め見|みてる？ 何|<な#|にも見|<みてない？
Couldn't be a dream, cause it feels like I'm awake
身处梦境吗？眼中却一无所见
yu me mi te ru na ni mo mi te na i
語|<か#|たるも無|<む駄|だな 自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの言|<こ#|と葉|ば？
Wish I have a better dream, cause my words don't carry weight
脱口而出也无用 连篇懊悔的废话
ka ta ru mo mu da na ji bun no ko to ba
悲|<か#|なしむなんて 疲|<つ#|かれるだけよ
I'm so sick of feeling sad, make it easy to regret
再怎么沉溺悲伤 也只是白费气力
ka na shi mu nan te tsu ka re ru da ke yo
何|<な#|にも感|<か#|んじず 過|<すごせばいいの
I'm so sick of 'good' and 'bad', it's so easy to forget
不妨让身体麻木 度过一天又一天
na ni mo kan ji zu su go se ba i i no
戸|<と惑|ま#|どう言|<こ#|と葉|ば 与|<あ#|たえられても
Even I don't understand every truth and every lie
即便被他人诉以 不知所云的言语
to ma do u ko to ba a ta e ra re te mo
自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの心|<こ#|こ#|ろ ただ上|<う#|わの空|<そ#|ら
I don't need to understand, if there's nothing left to hide
自己内心也依然 将其当作耳旁风
ji bun no ko ko ro ta da u wa no so ra
もし私|<わ#|た#|しから 動|<う#|ごくのならば
Toss my hope into the sky, and my chance of turning back
若是现在的自己 还有行动的余力
mo shi wa ta shi ka ra u go ku no na ra ba
すべて変|<かえるのなら 黒|<く#|ろにする
Maybe I can say goodbye, till I paint myself in black
不妨就让这一切 湮没于殷殷黑暗！
su be te ka e ru no na ra ku ro ni su ru
こんな自|<じ分|ぶ#|んに 未|<み来|ら#|いはあるの？
Do I see another day where I dream and be awake
对于我这样的人 是否还存在未来？
kon na ji bun ni mi ra i wa a ru no
こんな世|<せ界|か#|いに 私|<わ#|た#|しはいるの？
Do I see another day with my choices and my mistakes
这片广阔的世界 是否允许我存在？
kon na se ka i ni wa ta shi wa i ru no
今|<い#|ま切|<せ#|つないの？ 今|<い#|ま悲|<か#|なしいの？
Am I broken? Am I sad? No more tears for me to cry
此刻感到痛苦吗？此刻感到悲伤吗？
i ma se tsu na i no i ma ka na shi i no
自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの事|<こ#|とも わからないまま
If I don't know who I am, can't expect to feel alive
就连自己的一切 我也是云里雾里
ji bun no ko to mo wa ka ra na i ma ma
歩|<あ#|ゆむことさえ 疲|<つ#|かれるだけよ
Cause my heart is made of glass and my body made of stone
哪怕是踱步而行 也只是白费气力
a yu mu ko to sa e tsu ka re ru da ke yo
人|<ひ#|とのことなど 知|<しりもしないわ
Cause my life is made to last, so as long as I'm alone
对于他人的一切 我也是不甚了解
hi to no ko to na do shi ri mo shi na i wa
こんな私|<わ#|た#|しも 変|<かわれるのなら
Any choices I would have, if I had some tears to cry
若是这样的自己 还有改变的余地
kon na wa ta shi mo ka wa re ru no na ra
もし変|<かわれるのなら 白|<し#|ろになる？
If I think, therefore, I am, take a step into the light
若是还能够改变 我能回归纯洁吗？
mo shi ka wa re ru no na ra shi ro ni na ru
流|<な#|がれてく 時|<と#|きの中|<な#|かででも
Never figured out what it meant to keep on living
即便置身于 奔腾的时光长河中
na ga re te ku to ki no na ka de de mo
気|<けだるさがほら グルグル廻|<ま#|わって
Somewhere in my mind, spinning round and round in circles thinking
这份倦怠感 依旧萦绕在身难以消弭
ke da ru sa ga ho ra gu ru gu ru ma wa tte
私|<わ#|た#|しから離|<は#|なれる心|<こ#|こ#|ろも見|<みえないわ
Every single time - tell me what I'm missing
最初的本心 也已与我渐行渐远 难以再看清
wa ta shi ka ra ha na re ru ko ko ro mo mi e na i wa
そう 知|<しらない？
Is it somewhere deep inside, maybe I just lost it?
这样你明白吗？
so u shi ra na i
自|<じ分|ぶ#|んから 動|<う#|ごくこともなく
Even if I stay, never move, my body's frozen
只因我自己 早已不想作出改变
ji bun ka ra u go ku ko to mo na ku
時|<と#|きの隙|<す#|き|間|まに 流|<な#|がされ続|<つ#|づけて
Measure every day, every minute, every second slowly
任时光飞逝 自身投入其中随波逐流
to ki no su ki ma ni na ga sa re tsu zu ke te
知|<しらないわ 周|<ま#|わりのことなど
What you wanna say, doesn't make one difference
周遭的一切 皆已与我毫无瓜葛
shi ra na i wa ma wa ri no ko to na do
私|<わ#|た#|しは私|<わ#|た#|し それだけ？
Like I need to be okay, you don't have to save me
我也只是我自己 仅 此 而 已！
wa ta shi wa wa ta shi so re da ke
夢|<ゆ#|め見|みてる？ なにも見|<みてない？
Couldn't be a dream, cause it feels like I'm awake
身处梦境吗？眼中却一无所见
yu me mi te ru na ni mo mi te na i
語|<か#|たるも無|<む駄|だな 自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの言|<こ#|と葉|ば？
Wish I have a better dream, cause my words don't carry weight
脱口而出也无用 连篇懊悔的废话
ka ta ru mo mu da na ji bun no ko to ba
悲|<か#|なしむなんて 疲|<つ#|かれるだけよ
I'm so sick of feeling sad, make it easy to regret
再怎么沉溺悲伤 也只是白费气力
ka na shi mu nan te tsu ka re ru da ke yo
何|<な#|にも感|<か#|んじず 過|<すごせばいいの
I'm so sick of 'good' and 'bad', it's so easy to forget
不妨让身体麻木 度过一天又一天
na ni mo kan ji zu su go se ba i i no
戸|<と惑|ま#|どう言|<こ#|と葉|ば 与|<あ#|たえられても
Even I don't understand every truth and every lie
即便被他人诉以 不知所云的言语
to ma do u ko to ba a ta e ra re te mo
自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの心|<こ#|こ#|ろ ただ上|<う#|わの空|<そ#|ら
I don't need to understand if there's nothing left to hide
自己内心也依然 将其当作耳旁风
ji bun no ko ko ro ta da u wa no so ra
もし私|<わ#|た#|しから 動|<う#|ごくのならば
Toss my hope into the sky, and my chance of turning back
若是现在的自己 还有行动的余力
mo shi wa ta shi ka ra u go ku no na ra ba
すべて変|<かえるのなら 黒|<く#|ろにする
Maybe I can say goodbye, till I paint myself in black
不妨就让这一切 湮没于殷殷黑暗！
su be te ka e ru no na ra ku ro ni su ru
無|<む駄|だな時|<じ間|か#|んに 未|<み来|ら#|いはあるの？
Under pressure coming down, getting closer every day
在这虚无的时光 是否还存在未来？
mu da na ji kan ni mi ra i wa a ru no
こんな所|<と#|こ#|ろに 私|<わ#|た#|しはいるの？
Like an apple turning brown, getting further every day
现在到了这田地 我是否还能存在？
kon na to ko ro ni wa ta shi wa i ru no
私|<わ#|た#|しのことを 言|<いいたいならば
If I make another sound, if my mind is torn apart
若是将我的一切 用言语加以概括
wa ta shi no ko to o i i ta i na ra ba
言|<こ#|と葉|ばにするのなら「ろくでなし」
If I think about it now, I was broken from the start
那么一言以蔽之 不过是『无用之人』
ko to ba ni su ru no na ra ro ku de na shi
こんな所|<と#|こ#|ろに 私|<わ#|た#|しはいるの？
All I wanna see again are my dreams to stay awake
现在到了这田地 我是否还能存在？
kon na to ko ro ni wa ta shi wa i ru no
こんな時|<じ間|か#|んに 私|<わ#|た#|しはいるの？
All I wanna see again are my dreams with no mistakes
现在到了这时刻 我是否还能存在？
kon na ji kan ni wa ta shi wa i ru no
こんな私|<わ#|た#|しも 変|<かわれるのなら
Any choices I would have, if I had some tears to cry
若是这样的自己 还有改变的余地
kon na wa ta shi mo ka wa re ru no na ra
もし変|<かわれるのなら 白|<し#|ろになる？
If I think, therefore, I am, take a step into the light
若是还能够改变 我能回归纯洁吗？
mo shi ka wa re ru no na ra shi ro ni na ru
今|<い#|ま夢|<ゆ#|め見|みてる？ なにも見|<みてない？
But it couldn't be a dream, cause it feels like I'm awake
此刻身处梦境吗？眼中却一无所见
i ma yu me mi te ru na ni mo mi te na i
語|<か#|たるも無|<む駄|だな 自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの言|<こ#|と葉|ば？
Wish I have a better dream, cause my words don't carry weight
脱口而出也无用 连篇懊悔的废话
ka ta ru mo mu da na ji bun no ko to ba
悲|<か#|なしむなんて 疲|<つ#|かれるだけよ
I'm so sick of feeling sad, make it easy to regret
再怎么沉溺悲伤 也只是白费气力
ka na shi mu nan te tsu ka re ru da ke yo
何|<な#|にも感|<か#|んじず 過|<すごせばいいの
I'm so sick of 'good' and 'bad', it's so easy to forget
不妨让身体麻木 度过一天又一天
na ni mo kan ji zu su go se ba i i no
戸|<と惑|ま#|どう言|<こ#|と葉|ば 与|<あ#|たえられても
Even I don't understand every truth and every lie
即便被他人诉以 不知所云的言语
to ma do u ko to ba a ta e ra re te mo
自|<じ分|ぶ#|んの心|<こ#|こ#|ろ ただ上|<う#|わの空|<そ#|ら
I don't need to understand if there's nothing left to hide
自己内心也依然 将其当作耳旁风
ji bun no ko ko ro ta da u wa no so ra
もし私|<わ#|た#|しから 動|<う#|ごくのならば
Toss my hope into the sky, and my chance of turning back
若是现在的自己 还有行动的余力
mo shi wa ta shi ka ra u go ku no na ra ba
すべて変|<かえるのなら 黒|<く#|ろにする
Maybe I can say goodbye, till I paint myself in black
不妨就让这一切 湮没于殷殷黑暗！
su be te ka e ru no na ra ku ro ni su ru
動|<う#|ごくのならば 動|<う#|ごくのならば
If I make another move, if I make another move
如果我还能行动 如果我还能行动
u go ku no na ra ba u go ku no na ra ba
すべて壊|<こ#|わすわ すべて壊|<こ#|わすわ
Breaking everything I had, even if it isn't true
一切将灰飞烟灭 一切将灰飞烟灭
su be te ko wa su wa su be te ko wa su wa
悲|<か#|なしむならば 悲|<か#|なしむならば
Saving tears until I cry, saving tears until I cry
如果我还能感伤 如果我还能感伤
ka na shi mu na ra ba ka na shi mu na ra ba
私|<わ#|た#|しの心|<こ#|こ#|ろ 白|<し#|ろく変|<かわれる？
If I think, therefore, I am, I could step into the light
我的心是否还能 回归于纯洁无暇？
wa ta shi no ko ko ro shi ro ku ka wa re ru
貴|<あ#|な方|たの事|<こ#|とも 私|<わ#|た#|しのことも
I don't need to know about you, I don't need to know about me
无论是你的一切 抑或是我的一切
a na ta no ko to mo wa ta shi no ko to mo
全|<す#|べての事|<こ#|とも まだ知|<しらないの
I've been stuck inside a loop, you don't have to set me free
甚至所有的一切 我依旧无所知晓
su be te no ko to mo ma da shi ra na i no
重|<お#|もい目|<め蓋|<ふ#|たを 開|<あけたのならば
Once I open up my eyes, not a chance of turning back
若是我奋力睁开 这双沉重的眼睛
o mo i me fu ta o a ke ta no na ra ba
すべて壊|<こ#|わすのなら 黒|<く#|ろになれ
So it's time to say goodbye, cover everything in black
一切将灰飞烟灭 湮没于殷殷黑暗！！
su be te ko wa su no na ra ku ro ni na re